AFT Local 2 Records 5279
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Religious instruction: Committee, correspondence, 1937-1940 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Religious Released Time #1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Released Time #2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- AFT Executive Board - National (Box 11, Folder 1)
- AFT Materials to and from other locals (Box 11, Folder 2)
- AFT correspondence with locals (Box 11, Folder 3)
- AFT News, Press and publicity bulletins (Box 11, Folder 4)
- AFT national miscellaneous folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Folder on Eklund, John (Pres.) (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Folders (2) on Kuensli, Irving R. (Sec.-Treas., AFT) (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Folder on Megel, Carl (Pres.) (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Folder on Selden, David (AFT Field Representative) (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Folder on Mrs. Chas. Shipman (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Folder on Mrs. Rebeca Simonson (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Delegates Assembly Minutes, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- AFT Conventions, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- AFT Conventions, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- AFT Conventions, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- AFT Conventions, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- AFT Conventions, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Delegates Assembly Minutes, 1943-1946 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Delegates Assembly Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Delegates Assembly Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  And attendance
- Delegates Assembly Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Delegates Assembly Minutes, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Delegates Assembly Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Delegates, general correspondence with (Box 11, Folder 24)
- AFT per capita reports - receipts (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Allied Civil Service Conference (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Central Trades and Labor Council (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Joint Civil Conference and PEA, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Local #537, New York College Teachers Union (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Liberal Party (Box 12, Folder 5)
- NY State Department of Labor, Mediation Board (Box 12, Folder 6)
- NY State Education Department (Box 12, Folder 7)
- NY State Federation of Labor (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Public Education Association (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Rand School - Guild Cooperative Course (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Service Bureau for Intercultural Education (Box 12, Folder 11)
- UNESCO and United Nations (Box 12, Folder 12)
- White House Conference, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Womens Trade Union League (Box 12, Folder 14)
- World Organization of the Teaching Profession (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Empire State Federation of teachers Unions Correspondence, etc., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Jan. 1953
- Empire State Federation - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Empire State Federation of teachers Unions Correspondence, etc., 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Sept. 1950-1953
- Empire State Federation of teachers Unions Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Empire State Federation of teachers Unions Convention, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  November 8, 9, 1947
- Board of Education correspondence - A - E (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Board of Education correspondence - F - L (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Board of Education correspondence - M - R (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Board of Education correspondence - S - Z (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Board of Education, Miscellaneous, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Board of Education, Miscellaneous, 1950-1954 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Board of Education, Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Board of Education, Budget Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Correspondence - Gannon, Edmund J. (Personnel) (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Correspondence - Greenberg, Dr. Jacob (Dept. Supt.) (Box 12, Folder 30)
- AFT Convention resolutions - submitted by the Guild (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - Jansen, William (Superintendent) (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - Levitt, Arthur (Pres. B of E) (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Moss, Maximillian (Pres. B of E) (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Wade, John E. (Supt. of schools) (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Correspondence with Gov. Thomas E. Dewey (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Correspondence with Mayor Fiorello H. LaGuardia (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Correspondence with Mayor William ODwyer (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Correspondence with miscellaneous elected officials (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Correspondence - Dr. Abraham Lefkowitz (Box 13, Folder 10a)
- Correspondence - Dr. Abraham Lefkowitz (Box 13, Folder 10b)
- Correspondence - Dr. Abraham Lefkowitz (Box 13, Folder 10c)
- Correspondence - on Lefkowitz testimonial dinner (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - A Mark Levien (Legal Counsel) (Box 13, Folder 12a)
- Correspondence - A Mark Levien (Legal Counsel) (Box 13, Folder 12b)
- Correspondence - A Mark Levien (Legal Counsel) (Box 13, Folder 12c)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder B (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder C (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder D (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder E (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder G (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder H (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder I (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder L - M (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder N (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder P (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder S (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder T (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder V (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder W (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence - Folder X - Z (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Correspondence with NY University Student Council (Box 13, Folder 28)
- News Releases, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- News Releases, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- News Releases, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- News Releases, 1944-1945 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- News Releases, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Press Releases, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Press Releases, 1950-1954 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- AFT National Office - Bulletins, Releases, etc., 1946 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- AFT National Office - Bulletins, etc., 1948 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Letters to the Editor - NY Sun inter alia (Box 14, Folder 10)
- The Bulletin (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Inside Education (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Madison High School Teachers Guild Bulletin (Box 14, Folder 13)
- News from the Guild, Set of (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Past Thirty Days, Complete set (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Washington Newsletter (Box 14, Folder 16)
- The Washington Teacher (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Mimeographed News Letters from NYTG (Box 14, Folder 18)
- AFT General literature (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Pamphlets, miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Delegate Reporter - #1-44 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  to June 1951
- Delegate Reporter - #45-67 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  to June 1953
- Delegate Reporter - miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 3)
- New York Sun - Latest News In The Educational World", 1941 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  various issues in 1941
- New York Sun - Latest News In The Educational World", 1945 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  all issues of 1945
- Teachers Union News, 1942-1955 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  issues from Sept. 1951-Sept. 30, 1955; various issues from 1942 and 1943
- AFT Local 2 Constitution and releases (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Collection - Material against Board of Educations Informer Resolution (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook - clippings, 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Nov. 1946 - June 1947
- Scrapbook - publicity clippings, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  general publicity, Karelson resignation - emergency Comm., Quinn case, Colleges
- Scrapbook - newspaper clippings, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Scrapbook - Guild publicity, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Scrapbook - Membership Drive material, 1936-1938 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Scrapbook - Teachers Guild Association, 1936-1938 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Scrapbook - clippings, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Scrapbook - Membership Drive material, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Scrapbook - clippings, 1923-1925 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- AFT Amendments to National Convention (Box 18, Folder 1)
- AF of T Convention, 1918-1931 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- AFT Correspondence, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- AFT Federal Aid for Schools (Box 18, Folder 4)
- AFT Philadelphia, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- AFT Publicity and Literature, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Fall 1938
- AFT Financial Reports, 1920-1931 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- AFT Financial Reports, 1932-1936 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- AFT Financial Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- AFT Convention, Cedar Pt., OH, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Reports/Speeches/etc
- AFT Convention, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Aug. 1939
- AFT Conventions (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Prior to 1932
- AFT National Convention, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- AFT Financial Reports, 1920-1940 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- AFT Convention Reports (Box 19, Folder 9)
  1920's-1930's
- The American Teacher, 1936-1938 (Box 20, Folder 1a)
- The American Teacher, 1936-1938 (Box 20, Folder 1b)
- The American Teacher, 1936-1938 (Box 20, Folder 1c)
- Publicity & Literature, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Spring 1938
- AFT Releases (Box 20, Folder 3)
  no folder
- Arbitration Agreements (Box 21, Folder 1)